merchtable.com 2016-07-30

# Privacy Policy | Merchtable

## Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. This Statement of Privacy applies to the https://merchtable.com and Blue Collar Industries, INC. and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Blue Collar Industries, INC. include https://merchtable.com and Merchtable. The Merchtable website is aN ecommerce site. By using the Merchtable website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

## Collection of your Personal Information

Merchtable may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase Merchtable's products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. Merchtable may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age, gender, household income and General Interest Data. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Merchtable. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Merchtable website.

Merchtable encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Merchtable so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Merchtable is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Merchtable website.

## Use of your Personal Information

Merchtable collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

Merchtable may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Merchtable and its affiliates. Merchtable may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Merchtable does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Merchtable may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is transferred to the third party. Merchtable may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Merchtable, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Merchtable may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Merchtable, in order to determine what Merchtable services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Merchtable to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Merchtable will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Merchtable or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Merchtable; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Merchtable, or the public.

## Use of Cookies

The Merchtable website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Merchtable pages, or register with Merchtable site or services, a cookie helps Merchtable to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Merchtable website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Merchtable features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Merchtable services or websites you visit.

In order to better serve our customers, Merchtable uses Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. The data collected from these tools may include age, gender, and general interests. To opt out of this service please visit [this page](https://www.google.com/settings/ads) or install the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on by clicking [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

As you browse Merchtable.com, advertising cookies may be placed on your computer so that we can understand your interests. Our display advertising partners, including but not limited to AdRoll, Facebook, Vertical Mass, and Google, then enable us to present you with retargeting advertising on this and other sites based on your previous interaction with Merchtable. The techniques our partners employ do no collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. You can visit [this page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) for information on opting out of targeted advertising.

## Security of your Personal Information

Merchtable secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

## Children Under Thirteen

Merchtable does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website. This is a RocketLawyer.com document.

## Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Merchtable by contacting us here: \- Email: help@merchtable.com

## Changes to this Statement

Merchtable will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Merchtable encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Merchtable is protecting your information. Merchtable reserves the right to amend this Statement at our sole discretion and without prior notice. Your continued use of this website indicates your continued acceptance of these terms.

## Contact Information

Merchtable welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Merchtable has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Merchtable at:

Merchtable Blue Collar Industries, INC. 2220 Delaware St. Lawrence, Kansas 66046

Email Address: help@merchtable.com

Telephone number: 785 842 1319

_Effective as of March 30, 2016_
